<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Love on Blog c치 nh칙n</title>
    <link>https://hataketsu.github.io/categories/love/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Love on Blog c치 nh칙n</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <atom:link href="https://hataketsu.github.io/categories/love/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Old message from my ex</title>
      <link>https://hataketsu.github.io/oldmessage/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 16:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hataketsu.github.io/oldmessage/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;white-space: pre-wrap;&#34;&gt;
I guess I had enough time to think of shitty yesterday.
I remember I told you not to breathe a word about ours to anyone. So what do you wanna show off ? What do you think when inviting me with your friend ? Are you too serious ?
Well, you may not know, but I&#39;m still a young little girl, wearing a pink pyjama, sleeping with mom when being scared of murderers... I don&#39;t know how to behave &#34;properly&#34; in the presence of your friend. Cuz I&#39;m with you, not with your friend.
I guess, perhaps you&#39;re serious with me, and wanna introduce me to your friend ? If yes, thank you, but it&#39;s not my duty to keep up your appearance. So what did you blame on me ?
You have poor past but I don&#39;t ? Wanna a comparison between our tragedies ? Oh, maybe you don&#39;t have tragedies but me.
See, you&#39;re something really boring to others, but I see sth interesting inside you. You just want everyone see how poor you are ?? Have you ever care about how everyone injure around you ? You&#39;re really boring.
I don&#39;t force you to understand me, but do you think it necessary ? And I know a million people like you, trying to contact with nobody, wanting everybody know you clearly ?
All I acted was my natural essence. You want me to behave like this, my manner like that... I can&#39;t change myself and I don&#39;t want too.
Oh, I think I&#39;m happier with my girlfriends. And you&#39;d better find a more maturing girl than me, or the best is a man.
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>